24小时
第三季  第8集
前情提要
先让我说完
Just hear me out.
由于雪莉 你已经人心尽失
You used up the public's goodwill with Sherry.
他们不想知道你还和某些
They don't want to hear about you being involved
不值得信任的人相处
with someone else who's not trustworthy.
你得尊重你的选民
You have got to respect the people who voted for you.
他的前夫肯定有自己的目的
Her ex-husband clearly had his own agenda.
要证明他是个骗子应该不难
And it shouldn't be difficult to prove that he's a liar.
安 是我 泰德
Ann, it's me, Ted.
来我办公室见我 我会解释一切
Come up in my office. Come up and I'll explain everything.
我有文件能够证明你清白
I have some documents that will prove your innocence.
金是我 没人在旁边吧?
Kim, it's me. Are you alone?
你在哪儿? 查佩尔要你回来
Where are you? Chappelle ordered you back here.
在我找到你父亲前 我不会回来
I'm not coming back until I find your father.
我刚找到赫克托 萨拉扎的位置
I just found out where Hector Salazar is.
墨西哥北部拉斯涅韦斯小镇
Small town in northern Mexico called Las Nieves.
我相信杰克带拉姆正前往那里
I'm sure Jack's taking Ramon there now.
你不能孤身前往
You cannot go in there alone.
赫克托有一批人马等着
Hector's gonna have an army down there.
我要你保证 你不会让任何人知道我们的谈话
Kim, I need to hear you promise, you're not gonna tell anyone you talked to me.
多保重 蔡斯
Be careful, Chase.
你在干吗 杰克?
What are you doing, Jack?
你兄弟想在飞机上杀了我!
Your brother tried to kill me on the plane!
这和我们谈好的不一样!
That is not what we talked about.
兄弟
Hi, brother.
到底怎么回事? 我不明白
What's going on? I don't understand.
我保证马上给你解释
I'll tell you all about it in a minute. I promise.
干得不错杰克
Good job, Jack.
来吧 我们还有很多活要忙
Come. We have a lot of work to do.
查佩尔在哪儿?
Where's Chappelle?
-820审讯室  -我们走
-Interrogation 820.  -Let's go.
告诉我 你个狗娘养
Talk to me, you son of a bitch.
-阿尔梅达你来干嘛?  -让他出去
-Almeida, what are you doing here?  -Get him out of the room.
为什么?
Why?
-他潜进去了  -你在说什么?
-He's in.  -What are you talking about?
-谁潜进去了?  -杰克
-Who's in?  -Jack.
-什么?!  -盖尔和我一直在为杰克工作
-What?!  -Gael and I have been working with Jack.
我们试图让他潜回萨拉扎兄弟的组织
We've been trying to get him back undercover with the Salazars.
这个信号说明他已经成功了
That signal means he's back in.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我会解释的 现在我们得联系总统
I'll explain everything. Right now we got to call the President.
你是说鲍尔从头至尾在我们眼前做戏
So, you're telling me that Bauer's been playing a game with us all this time.
这不是做戏 瑞恩
It's no game, Ryan.
他又回到了萨拉扎家族
But he's back under with the Salazars.
而他们也信任他
And they trust him again.
我们赌的就是这个
That's what we're counting on, yeah.
我是你的上司 托尼
I'm your boss, Tony.
你应该先和我商量
You should have come to me first.
听着 瑞恩
Look, Ryan.
当我和总统解释完后 你会了解全部
You'll understand everything once I've explained it to the President.
如果那时你依旧认为我做错了
After that if you feel like I've acted inappropriately,
我任你处置
you can do what you got to do.
我会的
I will.
等着瞧
Count on it.
总统已经在线了
The President's coming in on the line.
谢谢
Thank you.
说吧 阿尔梅达先生
Go ahead, Mr. Almeida.
总统先生 我是托尼·阿尔梅达 洛杉矶的反恐局的总指挥
Mr. President, this is Tony Almeida director of CTU Los Angeles.
阿尔梅达先生
Mr. Almeida.
非常感谢您能接我电话 总统先生
Thank you for taking my call, Mr. President.
我的部门总管韦恩·帕默尔
You're also on with my chief of staff,
也在场
Wayne Palmer.
我听说这是紧急事件
I was told this was an urgent matter.
是的 长官
Yes, sir, it is.
这件事很复杂 我会尽量长话短说
It's also fairly complex so I'll try to keep it as clear and concise as I can.
继续
Go on.
今天所发生的一切
Sir, everything that's happened today,
从医疗中心的感染尸体
from the infected body at Health Services
到拉姆·萨拉扎的越狱都属于一次精心策划的苦肉计
through Ramon Salazar's prison break has been a part of an elaborate sting operation.
苦肉计?
Sting operation?
是的 由杰克·鲍尔 特工盖尔·奥尔特加和我
Yes, sir. Planned and executed by Jack Bauer,
策划并实施
agent Gael Ortega and myself.
说详细一点 阿尔梅达先生?
Elaborate, Mr. Almeida?
杰克·鲍尔 想亲自向您解释这个情况 长官
Jack Bauer wanted to fill you in on this situation himself, sir.
杰克·鲍尔是个流亡犯
Jack Bauer is a fugitive from the law.
恕我冒犯
If you indulge me sir,
有一份录像需要您过目
there's a video file you should see.
在反恐局服务器上
It's on a designated CTU server.
您输入密码d3d59后就能读取
You can access the file with the pass code, delta 3 delta 59
总统先生
Mr. President.
您能看到这段录像代表
The fact that you are viewing this recording now means that
我已经成功完成了计划的第一步
I have successfully completed the first phase of a secret operation.
和您所想的不同 萨拉扎组织并没有
Contrary to what you've been led to believe the Salazars are not
掌握科迪勒拉病毒
in possession of the Cordillera Virus.
是我刻意散布这个谣言
The idea that they are, is a lie which I promoted deliberately,
为了达到一个更重要的目的
in order to achieve a more important goal.
请允许我解释 长官
Please, sir, let me explain.
一个月前 我收到一份消息
About a month ago I learned from a contact
一小撮乌克兰的科学正试图在黑市上
that a group of scientists from the Ukraine were trying to sell a weaponized
出售病毒武器
virus on the open market.
他们想找有钱有信誉的买家
They were looking for a buyer with cash and credibility.
我唯有通过推荐萨拉扎组织
I only managed to get their interest when I suggested
才能得到对方的兴趣
the Salazars are potential buyers.
只要萨拉扎兄弟同意
As long as I can get the Salazars to agree,
反恐局就可以在交货时截获毒品
CTU would seize the virus as the sale took place.
我们的目的是在市场上根除货源
Our goal was to remove the virus stock pile from the market place.
总统先生 这毋庸置疑是
Because Mr. President it is without a doubt the most
我们所遇见过最致命的威胁
lethal threat that we have ever faced.
但事先必须让萨拉扎兄弟相信我已经叛变了
But all of this here has done convincing the Salazars that I have switched sides.
而唯一能争取他们信任的方法是 帮拉姆·萨拉扎脱狱
And the only way to get in their trust was to break Ramon Salazar out of prison.
总统先生...
Mr. President...
很抱歉我不得不瞒着您
I'm sorry for deceiving you.
但我保证绝无恶意
But I assure you it was a benign deception.
并且我会为我的行动负全责
And I assume complete responsibility for my actions.
如果此事败露 无论个人 法律还是政治上 您都会遇到重大打击
Sir, if things went wrong you would have been exposed personally, legally and politically.
这也是唯一能避免这种情况的办法
And this is the only way I could see to avoid that risk.
我请求您授权反恐局的负责人阿尔梅达配合军队进行突击
And I'm asking you to allow CTU director Almeida to coordinate an interdiction with the military
这样我们才能掌握病毒
so we can take possession of this virus
不致于让它落入敌手
and keep it from our enemies.
谢谢 总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
总统先生?
Mr. President?
在国家安全要件上瞒着我是不可原谅的
Keeping me in the dark on the matter of national security is inexcusable.
我们试图保护你 长官
We were trying to protect you, sir.
这我知道
I know what you were trying to do.
但这样做是错的
And it was a mistake.
事情结束后 你和你同事
And you and your colleagues will take responsibility for it,
-要承担责任  -我明白 长官
-when this is over.  -Yes, sir, I understand.
-鲍尔现在人呢?  -在墨西哥北部
-Where's Bauer now?  -In Northern Mexico.
他正在为萨拉扎组织和乌克兰的病毒贩卖者安排会面
He's setting up a meeting between the Salazars and the Ukrainians who are selling the virus.
什么时候他们会开始?
When is this meeting expected to take place?
几小时之后
In the next few hours, sir.
总统先生
Mr. President,
需要您的许可来组织突击
I'm requesting your permission to activate the interdiction plan.
在这种情况下 我不得不同意 阿尔梅达先生
Under the circumstances I don't have a choice but to say yes, Mr. Almeida.
但即使这个计划到目前为止天衣无缝...
But even if this plan works flawlessly...
你依旧不知道结果如何
you haven't heard the last of it.
我不喜欢别无选择的决定
I don't like decisions being taken out of my hands.
大卫有些决定最好不要沾边
Well, David some decisions you want to keep as far away as you can.
但这个不行 这件事太重要了
Not this decision, it's too important.
杰克·鲍尔没有权利将我排除在外
Jack Bauer had no right to keep me out of the loop.
我不这么看
I disagree.
鲍尔竭尽全力保护你
Bauer protected you as he should have.
事情结束后 你会从你的角度去惩罚他
And when this is all over you probably gonna have to punish him for form's sake
但是当你这么做的时候 记住...
But while you're punishing him, know this...
他并没有做错
He did do the right thing.
米歇尔
Michelle.
我们需要扩张信息网 用第4方案 行么?
We need extended network using protocol four, alright?
谢谢
Thanks.
我不确信一切会如你所愿 阿尔梅达
I'm not so sure this is gonna work out well for you Almeida.
也许吧
Maybe not,
但现在我得帮杰克弄到这个病毒
but right now I got to help Jack get this virus.
我不希望你一直在旁边看着我
And I don't need you looking over my shoulder, alright?
你是我下属
You work for me.
你只管接命令 不能发命令
You don't give orders, you take them.
明白
Yeah.
现在总统让我主管这次行动
Except the President put me in charge of this particular operation.
如果你有异议 你可以找他
Now if you object, give him a call.
我没估计错的话 我觉得他今天
I may be wrong, but I didn't get the impression
没有心情处理官僚内斗
that he's in the mood for any bureaucratic squabbling today.
瑞恩
Ryan,
让我把该干的干完 行么?
just let me do my job, alright?
好吧 我会旁观的
Yeah, I'll be watching.
你现在听得进去么 拉姆?
Are you ready to listen, Ramon?
好吧
Alright.
告诉我 这叛徒怎么会成了我们朋友
Tell me how the man betrayed us is now our friend.
鲍尔给我送来一个机会
Bauer came to me with an opportunity.
-机会?  -是的
-An opportunity?  -Yes.
去挣多到我们无法想象的钱
To make more money than we have ever dreamed of.
鲍尔找到一种即将上市的病毒
Bauer found out about a virus that was coming in the market.
那些人将把病毒带过来 他们是乌克兰人
These men will have it there, they are from the Ukraine.
是科学家
They're scientists.
他们只想拿了钱
All they want to do is to make their money
就走人
and disappear.
他们开价多少?
How much are they asking?
一个亿
A hundred million.
基地组织肯出10倍的价 朝鲜也是
Al Qaeda pays ten times as much North Koreans too.
我已经安排好了 很多人等着买
I made all the causable. I had the buyers all lined up.
那是10亿美金
That's a billion dollars.
你怎么知道这病毒不是幌子?
How do you know this virus is real?
乌克兰人给了我们展示品
The Ukrainians gave us a demonstration.
鲍尔把其中的一具尸体送到了洛杉矶的卫生部
Bauer delivered one of the bodies to Health Services in LA.
他借此恐吓美国政府放你走
He used it to scare the Americans to letting you go.
那些科学家 他们现在人在哪儿?
The scientists, where are they now?
他们就在附近
They're not far from here.
我应该在一小时内和他们的线人迈克尔 阿马多尔联系
I'm supposed to call their representative, a man named Michael Amador in the next hour.
这对你有什么好处 杰克?
What's in it for you, Jack?
1千5百万美金
50 million dollars.
拉姆 我们对彼此都有成见
Ramon, we don't like each other.
但这不意味我们不能合作
But it doesn't mean we can't do business together.
我需要你的信誉
I need your capital and
而你需要我的人脉来得到病毒
you need my access to the virus.
我从来没想过杰克·鲍尔会为钱干事
I will never have thought that Jack Bauer was for sale.
我妻子因为我的工作而被杀
My wife was killed because of my job.
我的女儿从此以后
My daughter's never been the same since.
像变了个人...
Just last year...
你知道我为了逮捕你付出了多大代价
well you know what I went through to bring you in.
结果我得到了什么?
What did I get for?
背一辈子的黑锅?
Pad on the back?
最后不仅被降级还惹上毒瘾
In the end the demotion and a heroine habit.
我已经厌倦了这样拼死拼活到头来什么都没有
I'm tired of putting my ass on the line for nothing.
我不想再这么干下去了
I'm done putting my ass on the line for nothing.
如果你不想和他合作
If you don't want to go through with it
崩了他
blow him away.
但要记得
But just remember,
你这一枪 也打飞了10亿美金
you're blowing away a billion dollars.
拉姆 不行!
Ramon, no!
-你疯了么?  -相信他才是发疯呢!
-Are you crazy?  -You are crazy for trusting him!
-给我枪  -不行
-Give me the gun.  -No.
你也想违抗我?
Who are you to refuse me?
是我照顾生意 不是你!
I run our business, not you!
如果不是我!
If not for me, me!
你就不会站在这儿
You wouldn't have been here.
如我所说...
Like I said...
在一小时内我得和他们联系
I have to call them within an hour.
那些人是不会等的
These men are not gonna wait around.
冒的风险太大
There's too much at stake.
你们要不毙了我
You can either shoot me
要不让我打电话
or let me make the call.
但你们最好尽快决定
But you'd better decide quickly.
杰克的跟踪器显示他位于
Jack's transponder pinpoints his location somewhere
拉斯涅韦斯东部 位于边境向南
east of Las Nieves just south of the border.
卫星显示那里是个大农场
Satellite photo shows that it is some sort of ranch or farm.
我们的部队会驻扎在10英里外
Our units will hold a perimeter of 10 miles.
所有的联络将通过特定频道
All communication will be on a designated frequency.
没我的指令不许轻举妄动 明白?
And nobody makes a move unless it goes through me first, alright?
克萝伊 我要你和蔡斯协助制定战术
Chloe, I want you and Chase provide tactical assistance.
-蔡斯在哪儿?  -不知道
-Where is Chase?  -We're not sure.
一小时前卡佩勒命令他回来
Chapelle ordered him back over an hour ago.
好极了 等他回来后通知我
Right, let me know when he gets back here.
这里我说清楚了
And let me make this perfectly clear.
几小时之内
For the next few hours
我们将尽全力
all of our resources are dedicated
帮杰克·鲍尔阻截病毒
to helping Jack Bauer intercept this virus.
还有什么问题?
Any questions?
大家回去工作吧
Alright, let's get back to work.
托尼
Tony.
我和蔡斯通过话
I spoke to Chase.
什么时候?
When?
一小时前 他不会回到反恐局
About an hour ago. He is not coming back to CTU.
你在说什么? 我以为卡佩勒已经命令他回来了
What are you talking about? I thought Chapelle gave him a direct order.
他无视了那个命令
He ignored it.
他目前还不清楚是怎么回事
He still doesn't really know what's going on.
和听到那番对话前的我们一样
None of us did until you spoke to the President.
蔡斯依旧认为我父亲是被萨拉扎他们绑架了
Chase still thinks my father was captured by the Salazars.
因此他要前往拯救杰克.
And he thinks he's going in to rescue Jack.
没错 他已经找到拉斯涅韦斯 现在正赶往那里
Yes. He knows about Las Nieves, he's on his way there right now.
应该是坐飞机
Probably by plane.
他怎么找到拉斯涅韦斯的?
How the hell did he find out about Las Nieves?
他说从一个线人那里
He said he followed a lead.
该死的! 如果他一去 杰克的身份就暴露了
Damn it! If he goes in, he's gonna blow Jack's cover
-那我们就拿不到病毒了  -我知道
-and we're gonna lose this virus.  -I know.
-好吧 也许我能联系到他  -托尼 这办不到
-Alright, maybe I can get hold of him.  -Tony, you won't be able to reach him.
-为什么?  -没办法联系上他
-Why not?  -He's gone dark.
赫克托估计你饿了
Hector thought you might be hungry.
看看你自己
Look at you.
你简直可悲!
You're pathetic!
和渣滓没什么两样
Looks like a junk are you.
这就是你的本质
It's the only real thing about you.
我简直不无法想象我曾经相信过你
It makes me sick to think that I ever believed you.
你说过你会带我离开这里
You said you'd take me away from here.
记得么?
Remember?
还记得么 杰克?
Do you remember, Jack?
是的 我还记得
Yes, I remember.
其实你只有一件事没有明说...
Well there is one small thing you forgot to mention...
你是个警察
You were a cop.
但是我不在乎 只要你还能记住一丁点承诺
But even that wouldn't matter if you meant half the things you said to me.
我对你所说的话 都是真心诚意的
I meant everything I ever said to you.
你以为我是笨蛋么?
Do you think I am stupid?
你只是在应付公事!
You were doing a job!
你对我的恭维毫无破绽
My compliments, you did it very well.
但你最悲哀的是什么知道么 杰克?
But you know the saddest thing, Jack?
你的话你自己都不相信
You couldn't even be true to that.
你背叛了赫克托和拉姆
You betrayed Hector and Ramon,
背叛了我
betrayed me.
而现在你背叛了你的人民
And now you betray your own people.
天知道我有多鄙视赫克托
God knows there are times when I despise Hector
但至少他从来不欺骗自己
but at least he's true to himself.
他有自知之明 你呢?
He knows who he is. You?
你不过就是一具行尸走肉
You're a man without a soul.
赫克托知道我们的关系么?
Does Hector know about us?
如果他发现了 我还能活命么?
Do you think I'd be alive if he did?
你知道他现在在干吗?
You know where he is right now?
他和拉姆在一起
He's with Ramon,
决定你的生死
deciding whether you should live or die.
而你却在一旁瑟瑟发抖
But you sit here shaking like a leaf.
你想嗑药么?
You need a fix, don't you?
我可以给你 你想要的 杰克.
Well there's plenty here, Jack.
你要我给你带药么?
You want me to get you a fix?
这是你想要得么?
Is that what you want?
不
No.
杰克
Jack.
你曾经是个男子汉
You were a man once.
到底怎么了?
What happened to you?
好 我把他的照片发给你
Right, I'm sending his photo to you, right now.
-好了  -记住 米格尔
-Okay.  -Remember, Miguel,
此人是擅自行动
this guy's acting on his own authority.
记得告诉古铁雷斯他不是危险分子
Make sure you tell Gutierrez that he's not dangerous.
好的 我会与你联系
Okay. I will confirm with you.
很好
Right, good.
我刚和墨西哥的情报处通过话
I just spoke to my contact in Mexican Intelligence.
他说20分钟内 他会派人前往拉斯涅韦斯
He says he can send a man in Las Nieves in less than 20 minutes.
名叫拉斐尔·古铁雷斯的特工
An agent named Rafael Gutierrez.
地方警察不是会更快么?
Won't local police be quicker?
如果我们派他们去 等于是给萨拉扎通风报信
No. If we bring them in we might as well send a telegram to the Salazars
蔡斯正在路上
that Chase is on his way.
特种部队呢?
What about our delta teams?
不行 这至少要花一个小时 到那时就太晚了
No, it's gonna take them over an hour. It'll be way too late.
我们正在分析拉斯涅韦斯地区分布
We're analyzing the areal map of Las Nieves.
那里只有一个飞机跑道
There's only one landing strip.
他不会用的
He won't use it.
用飞机跑道着陆太暴露 何况这还是唯一一个
Landing strip's too exposable. Especially if it's the only one.
好吧 做个地面图形分析
Alright. Run a topographical overlay.
找出最有可能着陆的地方
Find the mostly likely landing area the size of the airfield.
怎么了 大卫?
Yes, David?
你有安妮的消息么?
Have you seen or heard from Anne?
有段时间没消息了 怎么?
Not for some time. Why?
我联系不到她
I can't reach her.
是你的健康问题么?
Is this about your health?
不 我在担心她
No. I'm concerned about her.
辩论之后 她受的打击不小
She was pretty ripped up after the debate.
我们也一样 大卫
We're all pretty ripped up here, David.
听着 安妮前夫所放出的流言可不是鸡毛蒜皮的小事
Listen, this allegation by Anne's ex-husband is no small bump in the road.
我想到现在依旧没能找到
Now I've been thinking about this and there may be no way
合理的说辞来应对基勒的质问
to defend ourselves against Keeler's accusation and
并解释安妮的违法问题
Anne was involved in something illegal.
你不能这么敷衍了事 韦恩
You have to do better than that, Wayne.
我知道你总是勇于直面问题
I know you like to deal things head on.
但是 目前最好的做法是避其锋芒
But I think the best course of action for right now is to be evasive.
如果舆论提起这事 你得表明
So if the press brings this up you make it clear that
你不会回答任何问题
you're not gonna answer any questions.
等到所有证据各就各位
That you are gonna wait for all the facts to come in as should they.
也许你没说错 但是与此同时 我要你找到安妮
Well you may be right but in the meantime I need you to find Anne.
记者们会缠着她 她不擅长应付这些
The reporters are gonna be chasing her and she's not up to this.
我会让佩里解决这个
I'll put Perry on it.
谢谢
Thank you.
你好安妮
Hello, Anne.
谢谢你能来
Thanks for coming.
我只是希望能有机会亲自向你道歉
I just wanted to have a chance to apologize face to face for what I did.
我那时不知道自己在做什么
I don't know what I was thinking.
你说的信呢 泰德?
Where are the letters, Ted?
这里
Right here.
我向上帝起誓 安妮
For god's sakes, Anne.
这不是为你准备的
It's not meant for you.
那是为谁?
No, for whom then?
带着信走就是了
Just take the letters and go.
泰德?
Ted?
-你不是准备自杀吧?  -当然不是!
-You're not going to kill yourself, are you?  -Oh, no!
-这是为了自卫  -不要骗我
-It's for self defense.  -Don't lie to me.
听着 你已经拿到你想要的了
Look, you got what you came for.
所以快走 你不用管这事
So go! You don't need to be here for this.
至少找个人谈谈
At least talk to someone.
我知道一些不错的医生
I know some good doctors.
花钱请那些蠢货来劝我 放弃这五年前就该做的事吗
High priced phonies are gonna talk me out of doing what I should have done 5 years ago?
不 多谢了
No, thank you.
我是个失败的人 安妮
I'm a failure, Anne.
我什么都干不好
Everything I touch goes bad.
就是这么回事
It's just the way it is.
别为我哭泣 我不配
Don't shed any tears for me because I don't deserve it.
离开吧
Just... just go.
别过来
Don't come any closer.
-让我叫人来  -不行!
-Let me call someone.  -No!
求你了...
Please...
你是个伟大的女人 安妮
Now you're a great woman, Anne.
我配不上你 对不起让你失望
Much better than I ever deserved and I'm sorry I let you down.
但现在请你快出去
But just get the hell out of here.
我叫你走!!
I said go!!
-你没必要这么做  -没必要?
-It doesn't have to be like this.  -No?
怎么可能?
How can it be?
难道我们还能重回25岁么?
Can we be 25 again?
你当初确实犯了错
What you did was wrong.
但是你已经改过自新
But you made it right.
这很重要
And that means something.
这代表你还能补救
That means you can start again.
人人如此 泰德
People do it all the time, Ted.
为什么你不尝试?
Why not you?
你确实不同寻常
You're really something.
也许我再给你几分钟
I believe if I gave you a few more minutes,
你就能说服我放弃自杀
you might actually be able to talk me out of doing it.
泰德...
Ted...
别!
No!
总统可以从我这里得到最新消息
The President can expect updates directly from me.
我们多久联系一次?
How often do we call you?
-每15分钟  -我会转告他的
-Every 15 minutes.  -I'll let him know.
好 保持联络
Alright, we'd be in touch.
你该呆在医院
You should be in the hospital.
我没事
I'm fine.
你带了什么?
What have you got?
拉斯涅韦斯概况报告
Briefing package on Las Nieves.
除了飞机跑道外 蔡斯可能采用的其它着陆点
Alternate landing sites that Chase might use instead of the air strip.
谢谢
Thanks.
出了什么事?
Is there something wrong?
只是担心你而已
Just worried about you, that's all.
怎么了?
What is it?
现在不合适
It's not the time.
米歇尔.
Michelle
怎么了?
What is it?
你和杰克所密谋的这一切
This whole thing you've been planning with Jack...
听着...
Look...
我很抱歉 没能告诉你
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you.
杰克计划的一切 我和他同意要绝对保密
Jack planned it and he wanted absolute secrecy and I agreed.
-你没必要解释  -不 让我说
-You don't have to explain.  -No, I want to explain.
听着
Listen to me.
我能把生命托付给你
I trust you with my life.
但是这个活就是这样
But this job is what it is.
杰克说这个计划是他一个月前想到的
Jack said he came up with the plan a month ago.
你从那时就知道么?
Is that how long you've known?
差不多
Something like that. Yeah.
我只是...
I just...
一点都不知道
I had no idea
你背地里瞒着我
you were hiding something from me.
但那是我的问题
But that's my problem.
刚和反恐局通过话
Just got off the phone with CTU.
鲍尔已经接近拉斯涅韦斯
Bauer's near a place called Las Nieves.
特种部队正在赶往的途中
Delta teams are scrambling now.
反恐局什么时候能截获乌克兰人的病毒
When does CTU expect to intercept the virus from the Ukrainians?
只要鲍尔一给信号
As soon as Bauer gives them a signal.
托尼·阿尔梅达说每隔15会与我们联络
Tony Almeida says he'll be giving us an update every 15 minutes.
-很好  -我是韦恩·帕默尔
-Good.  -It's Wayne Palmer.
对
Yeah.
等下
Yeah, hang on.
大卫 是安妮打来的 她说有要事
David, it's Anne. She says it's important.
喂 安妮?
Hello, Anne?
大卫?
David?
泰德出事了
It's Ted.
他刚刚自杀
He just committed suicide.
安妮 我对此很遗憾
Oh, Anne. I'm so sorry.
你还好么?
Are you alright?
不完全 我...
Not really, no. I was umm...
我看着他自杀的
I was with him when he did it.
你在那里做什么?
What were you doing there?
他想见我 大卫 他说对不起我
He asked to see me, David. He said that he was sorry
他说想弥补
and that he wanted to make things right.
-而我...  -你通知警察了么?
-And I...  -Did you call the police?
-是的 他们已经到了  -我能帮什么忙么?
-Yes, they're here now.  -What can I do to help?
有些东西我想交给你
Well there's something that I need to give you.
泰德想让我转交给你
Something Ted wanted me to give you.
什么东西?
What's that?
是信
It's letters that umm...
它能帮我免除一切不利证据
exonerate me from any connection to the falsified research data.
这也是我为何在那里 因为他想给我这些
That's why I was here on the first place. Because he wanted to give them to me.
-你现在拿到那些信了  -是的
-And you have these letters.  -Yes, I do.
因此 我将会清白 而且...
So, I'll be in the clear and...
希望能挽回你的劣势
hopefully puts an end to the negative fall for you as well.
这些和你的安危相比只是其次
That's secondary to you're well being.
我会好的
I'll be okay.
处理完这边的事 我就来找你
I'll come over as soon as I'm done here.
好 过会见
Good. I'll see you then.
好
Okay.
一切还好么?
Is everything alright?
泰德 帕卡德刚刚自杀
Ted Packard just committed suicide.
当着安妮面
And he did it in front of Anne.
天啊 大卫 我恨遗憾
Oh, my god, David. I'm so sorry.
听着 我不想...
Listen I don't mean to...
我不想这么说 但是她去找他干吗?
I don't mean to sound callous but what was she doing with him?
他想给她信件
He wanted to give her letters.
这些信件能证明她的清白
Which will apparently prove she's innocent.
你说真的?
You're serious?
她马上就会把信带过来
She's gonna bring them over in a while.
我想这算是不幸中的万幸了
Well I guess that's some sort of silver lining it.
听着
Listen,
大卫 我知道我对安妮很不客气
David I know I've been somewhat hard on Anne.
但是她已经解决了自己的问题 我对此很敬佩
But she cleaned up her own mess and I respect that.
也许她明白在这种生活中不能那么随心所欲
Maybe she's learned what it takes to be in this game after all.
我们要鲍尔干吗?
Why do we even need Bauer?
因为他和乌克兰科学家首先联系的
Because he made the first contact with the Ukrainian scientists.
他们想和他交易 他们相信他
They want to deal with him. They trust him.
你也相信他
You trust him too.
相信那个伪装成我们朋友 并将我关入监狱的人
The man who pretended to be our friend and then put me in prison.
-但是你现在出来了!  -他有目的的 赫克托
-And got you out again!  -He has an angle, Hector.
-相信我  -当然他有目的!
-Count on it.  -Of course he does!
1千5百万不是小数目
50 million dollars is a big angle.
你也看见了
You saw him.
他已经是行尸走肉了
He's a shell, there's nothing left.
没有未来 没有家庭
No future, no family.
外加一辈子戒不掉的毒瘾
And a habit he can't beat.
他已经不是曾经把我们耍得团团转的人了
He's not the same man who fooled us before.
你这么确定?
So sure of that?
你知道我们在美国情报局有内线
You know we have people in the American agencies.
军队里也有
In the military too.
所有的人都确认 是真的越狱
All of them, every one of them confirmed the prison break was real.
鲍尔已经成了他祖国的通缉犯
Bauer is a fugitive from his own country.
如果不是为了活捉你 他们一定会杀了他
If they hadn't wanted you alive they would have killed him.
这是事实
That's a fact.
那么一切结束之后 我们怎么做?
So, if we go through with this, what happens afterwards?
我们就忘掉鲍尔过去的事?
We just forget what Bauer did to us
然后看着他走掉?
and let him walk away?
你以为我会原谅他的所作所为么?
Do you think I can forget what he did to us?
只要病毒一到手...
As soon as we have the virus...
我们就杀了他
we kill him.
这是你说到现在 我唯一喜欢听的一句
Now that's the first thing you said that I like.
鲍尔是个聪明人
Now Bauer is clever
他会想到的
and he'll expect it.
他能怎么样? 在这里孤立无援
And what can he do? Alone, surrounded.
别低估他
Don't underestimate him.
被低估的人是我 拉姆
It's me who's been underestimated, Ramon.
但是我会得到你的认同
But I will earn your respect.
当我们一天挣的钱比我们一辈子还多时
When we make more money in one day than we've made in both of our lifetimes.
但是你不能考虑一晚上
But you don't have all night to decide.
阿马多尔正在等鲍尔的电话
This man Amador is waiting for Bauer's call.
-带鲍尔进来  -马上 拉姆
-Bring Bauer in.  -Right away, Ramon.
你怎么决定 拉姆?
What have you decided, Ramon?
我还不清楚
I'm not sure yet.
我永远不会信任你
I don't trust you and I never will.
我现在只想让你血溅当场
All I want right now is to spill your blood.
但是至少现在不是时候
But I won't. Not yet anyway.
出于对我弟弟的尊重
Out of respect for my little brother,
我会和你再玩一会
I am willing to play this out a little longer.
打电话吧
So make your call.
阿马多尔每次通话后15分钟内就会换号码
Amador won't be at the number he gave me for another 15 minutes.
我们能等
We'll wait.
你不会后悔的
You won't be sorry.
托尼 在拉斯涅韦斯的拉斐尔打来电话
Tony, it's Rafael from Las Nieves.
接过来
Patch me over here.
喂 拉斐尔
Yeah, Rafael.
我现在已经抵达着陆点
Yeah, I'm at the landing area now.
没有看见任何的飞机
There's no sign of any incoming craft.
你队里一共多少人?
What size team do you have?
什么队伍? 就我一个
What team? It's just me.
你开玩笑吧
You got to be kidding me.
这里可是危险地带
Look, this is a corrupt area.
萨拉扎在这儿的影响很大 大到无法想象
Salazar's got a lot of influence here, we don't know how far it reaches.
米格尔要我单独干
Miguel wanted me to do this on my own.
好吧 那你有的忙了
Alright, well you're gonna have your hands full
蔡斯是我们这儿最有能耐的特工之一
cause Chase's one of our more capable agents.
你要我怎么接近他?
Alright, how do you want me to approach?
别惊动他
Well don't surprise him.
让他知道你是反恐局的帮手
Make sure he knows you're working with CTU.
这肯定是他
Yeah, this must be him.
有一架双引擎的飞机正在靠近
It's a twin engine prop on approach.
他正在着陆
He's landing now.
你看过我们发的照片了么?
You have the photo we sent you?
对
Yeah.
确保你没有找错人 小心点
Make sure it's him, be careful.
别挂线
We'll keep this line open.
好
Good.
我行动了
Alright, I'm moving in.
多加小心
Right, be careful.
他不想被发现
He's not expecting company.
埃德蒙兹.
Edmunds
埃德蒙兹我是来帮忙的
Edmunds. I'm here to help.
埃德蒙兹?
Edmunds?
古铁雷斯 说话
Gutierrez, talk to me.
他不在这儿
He's not here.
飞机是空的
The plane's empty.
他一定看见你了
He must have spotted you.
估计是了
It's that way.
我会给你回话
I'll call you back.
好
Yeah, alright.
埃德蒙兹!
Edmunds!
埃德蒙兹?
Edmunds?
等等! 别冲动!
Wait, wait, wait! Take it easy!
-你到底是谁?  -我是拉斐尔·古铁雷斯
-Who the hell are you?  -My name in Rafael Gutierrez.
墨西哥情报局
Mexican Intelligence.
你翻我的口袋 左边的的那个!
Check my pocket, my left pocket. Check it!
跪下来 双手抱头
Down on your knees. Hands behind your head.
-十指交叉  -好吧
-Lock your fingers.  -Alright.
-你怎么知道我的名字?  -是你上司让我来找你的
-How do you know my name?   -Your boss sent me to find you.
托尼·阿尔梅达 隶属反恐局 他的证件号为3t664
Tony Almeida, CTU. His access code is 3 tango 664.
起来
Get up.
他有什么事?
What does he want?
他有话和你说
He wants you to call him.
我有手机
I've got a phone right here.
他说这事关杰克·鲍尔的生死
He says it's a matter of life or death about Jack Bauer.
给我电话
Give me the phone.
谢谢
Thank you.
-阿尔梅达  -我是埃德蒙兹
-Almeida.  -It's Edmunds.
听着 蔡斯...
Listen, Chase...
如果你想叫我回去 那是在浪费
If you're trying to get me to come back, you're wasting...
蔡斯!
Chase!
蔡斯 怎么了?
Chase, what's going on?
蔡斯 听得见么?
Chase, can you hear me?
托尼 听得见么?
Tony, are you there?
-怎么了?  -你派来的人死了
-What's going on?  -The guy you sent is dead.
被狙击手干掉了
A sniper took him out.
有人在追杀我
I'm being pursued.
蔡斯!?
Chase!?
蔡斯?
Chase?
听得见么? 蔡斯?
Can you hear me? Chase?
帕卡德医生?
Doctor Packard?
我有事找总统
I'm supposed to see the President.
跟我来 女士
Follow me, ma'am.
进来!
Come!
安妮.
Anne
-你情况怎么样?  -还好
-How are you holding up?  -Okay.
这是那些信么?
Are those the letters?
好极了大卫 好极了
This is good David. This is very good.
这能澄清一切
This clears up everything.
没错
Yes, yes it does.
一旦这些经过验证 我们就会把它们交到媒体手上
Once these get authenticated we'll take them to the press.
这样矛头就会从你转向基勒
You'll be off the hook and Keeler should be hoisted right up on it.
我觉得你会很高兴
Yeah, I thought you'd be pleased.
安妮 听我说...
Anne, listen umm...
我对泰德感到遗憾
I'm sorry about Ted.
我说真的 如果...
I really am and if there's...
有任何我可以帮忙的事情
anything that I can do.
任何事...
Anything at all please just...
请告诉我
Let me know.
谢谢
Thank you.
失礼了
Excuse me.
安妮?
Anne?
我没事大卫 我不会有事的 不过
I'm alright, David. I'm gonna be alright. But
因为这件事
something came out of this.
我突然意识到了
And it was suddenly so clear to me.
意识到什么?
What was clear?
我觉得除了明说别无他法
I don't know how to say this except to just say it.
我觉得我们应该结束了
I think we need to end things.
刚刚发生了这种事...
After what's just happened...
经历了这样的一天
After what's been happening all day
我可以理解你需要独处一会
I can understand why you want some time apart.
大卫 我不是指独处一会
David, it's not about time apart.
-安妮...  -今天确实很糟糕
-Oh, Anne...  -And it is true today has been awful.
但是...
But...
这让我确信了之前一直纠缠我的感觉
It just confirmed something that I have been feeling for a while.
我无法进入你的世界
I can't live in your world.
人们之间的所作所为
The things that people do to each other.
为了生存而不择手段
The things they have to do in order to survive.
我只是...
I just...
-我没法...  -这就是我需要你的原因
-I can't...  -That's exactly why I need you.
你需要一个能够支持你的人
You need someone who can stand beside you.
而不是 某个躲在背后...
Not someone who stands back and watches and...
只会对自己不懂的事情指手划脚的人
Or maybe passes judgment on things she doesn't really understand.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你是我所见到最完美的男人
You are the finest man I have ever known.
而韦恩 上帝保佑他
And Wayne, god bless him.
他正是你所需要的类型 我很高兴你身边有他
He's just what you need and I'm so glad you have him.
但是... 我不适合这一切
But...  it's not for me.
别了 大卫
Goodbye, David.
安妮!
Anne!
-喂?  -迈克尔! 我是杰克·鲍尔
-Hello?  -Michael! It's Jack Bauer.
-能听见么?  -听得到 杰克
-Can you hear me?  -I can hear you, Jack.
我很高兴你平安抵达
I'm glad you arrived safely.
你在哪儿?
Where are you?
你知道我不会说的 杰克
You know I can't tell you that, Jack.
好吧 那告诉我哪里碰头?
Okay fine then where do you want to meet?
几分钟后我会答复你
I'll call you back in a few minutes.
把你现在的号码给我
Give me the number you're calling from.
这是卫星电话 等一下
Okay, I'm on a satellite phone. One second.
号码是 3-4-2-2-1
Number's 3-4-2-2-1.
-我很快会给你回电  -好
-You'll hear from me soon.  -Okay, good.
准备好你的钱
You better have your money prepared.
别担心
Don't worry about that.
他坐飞机来的
He came in by plane.
在镇南面着落
Just south of the town.
他和他们杀掉的联邦特工在一起
He was with a federally that they killed.
我认识他
I know this man.
他是杰克·鲍尔的搭档
It's Bauer's partner.
-还有其它人么?  -不 就他和联邦特工
-Was he with anyone else?  -No, just the federally and him.
-你在这里干什么?  -闭嘴!
-What the hell are you doing here?  -Hey, shut up!
如果他在这里 意味着其他人也快到了
If he's here, others will be here soon.
我们得转移了
We got to get out of here.
托马斯 去做好准备
Thomas, make sure everything is ready.
我们现在就要转移!
We're moving out of here, now!
鲍尔一直在骗人
Bauer has been lying to us all along.
不是这样的! 我根本不知道他会来
That's not true! I had no idea he was coming down here.
你又在耍我们了!
You've been playing us for fools again!
拉姆 你在酿成大错
Ramon, you're making a mistake.
赫克托 求你了
Hector, please.
我们要做这桩生意
We can still do this deal.
别让你兄弟搞砸了10亿美金
Don't let your brother piss away a billion dollars.
你怎么知道他是否在撒谎?
You know what if he's telling the truth?
他只说你想听的话
You keep hearing what you want to hear.
他是在演戏 整个都是在演戏!
This is an act. It's all been an act!
你怎么知道?
How do you know?
拉姆 我向你发誓
Ramon I swear to you,
我没在撒谎
I'm not lying.
让我们合作吧
Please, let's do this deal.
-这到底是怎么回事 杰克?  -闭嘴 蔡斯!
-What the hell is going on here, Jack?  -Shut up, Chase!
你根本不该跟踪我
You should have never followed me down here.
你和他们一伙?
You're with them?
没错 我和他们是一伙的
Yes, I'm with them.
你说他跟你没关系
You say he's not with you.
没错
Yes, that's right.
那就杀给我看
Then kill him.
杀了你搭档
Kill your partner.
你要我杀? 好 我能杀
You want me to kill him? Fine, I'll kill him.
但是 如果从他身上审问情报 甚至
But we would be smarter to use him for information
拿他当人质不是更加明智?
and maybe even as a hostage.
别给我油嘴滑舌!
No more clever talk!
你既然一直声称和我们一伙
You keep saying you're on our side.
那现在就证明给我们看
Now prove it, once and for all.
好吧
Fine.
你根本不该来 蔡斯
You should have never come down here, Chase.
你应该听从我的劝告
You should have listened to me.
很好 杰克
Very good, Jack.
我们会带着他
We'll take him with us.
鲍尔没错
Bauer is right.
让我们看看他知道什么
Let's find out what he knows.
好好拷问他 看看是否有其他人跟来
Break him down. See if anyone came here with him.
我们去个避难所
We'll go up to a safe house.
等阿马多尔来电话
And we'll wait for Amador's call.
-杰克  -闭嘴 蔡斯!
-Jack.  -Shut up, Chase!
你如果还想活命 就给我闭嘴!
You want to get through this? Just shut up!
该死!
Damn it!
托尼 不知怎么的杰克的手表发信器坏了
Tony. I don't know how but the transponder on Jack's watch just went dead.
-你试过重置么?  -试过了
-Did you try reset?  -Yeah.
没用
Nothing.
该死的!
Damn it!
即使突击部队就位 我们也根本不知道他身在何处
By the time the assault teams are in position we'll have no idea where he is.